OMIRIN ADEBAYO

odysseusoma.hashnode.dev | adebayoomirin@gmail.com | odysseusoma.github.io

REACT DEVELOPER / TECHNICAL WRITER

I'm a frontend developer with 4+ years of experience in JavaScript/ES6 and UI/UX design. My specialties include React, Vue, Angular, and CMS platforms like WordPress, Squarespace, and WIX. I'm also a skilled technical writer, with experience producing accurate and accessible documentation, as well as instructional content and tutorials.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer | Kitarific

Jun 2023 - Jan 2024

- Building and maintenance of websites and e-commerce platforms
- Ensure the application is responsive and accessible across different devices and platforms.
- Debug and troubleshoot issues that arise in the client websites and provide timely solutions.

Mobile App Developer | TaskGenie

May 2023 - Aug 2023

- Full stack developer responsible for frontend development, cloud storage, and backend compatibility
- Design, creation, and implementation of prototypes
- Responsible for brainstorming for new features
- Write unit tests to ensure code quality and minimize regressions.

Fullstack Developer | PROP44

Feb 2023 - May 2023

- Building and maintenance of frontend application and subsequent updates
- Ensure the application is responsive and accessible across different devices and platforms.
- Debug and troubleshoot issues that arise in the application and provide timely solutions.

Lead Fullstack Engineer | Consolt

Sept 2021 - Dec 2022

- Full stack web developer responsible for frontend development, cloud storage and backend compatibility
- Design, creation, and implementation of prototypes
- Responsible for brainstorming for new features

Freelance Frontend Developer |

March 2019 - present

• Building and maintenance of frontend application and subsequent updates

SKILLS

- HTML
- REACT
- NODE
- PHP

- CSS
- TYPESCRIPT
- GIT
- LARAVEL

- JAVASCRIPT
- MONGO DB
- RESTFUL API
- REACT NATIVE

EDUCATION

BEng Mechanincal Engineering | University of Ilorin

Oct 2017 - Oct 2023

INTERESTS

- Simulation Design
- Chess
- Volunteer Work

- Music
- Technical writing
- Football